Hi everyone. In this video, I'm going to
show you how to delete and archive tasks
and lists in Blitzet. Two handy ways to
keep your workspace tidy and organized.
To delete a task, simply hover over the
task you want to remove, open the
expanded menu, and click delete. Keep in
mind that this is permanent. Deleted
tasks cannot be recovered and won't show
up in your reports where you track your
progress. When it comes to lists, the
process is a bit different. Instead of
deleting right away, you first archive
it. Click the three dot menu next to the
list name and select archive list.
Archiving and moves the list out of your
active workspace, but keeps it safe for
later. Your archived lists will appear
in the archived list section on the left
side of your home screen. From there,
you can choose to unarchive the list to
make it active again, or click delete
forever to remove the list and all of
its tasks. Just be sure you really don't
need it anymore as this action cannot be
undone.
You can also go to the archived done
tasks section here. It is a list of the
tasks which are done and are older than
60 days. So they get automatically
archived.
So that's your quick guide to deleting
and archiving tasks and list in Blitzet.
For more tips and support, don't forget
to explore our other tutorials and join
our Discord community. We'd love to see
you there. Happy Blitzing.